Juice by Tappy! Juice by Tappy! Juice by Tappy!
ohhh, Tappy's got juice! Tappy's got juice!
Whoa, Tappy!
Juice! Juice! Juice!
Juice by you! Juice by you!
Juice! Juice by you! Thank you, thank you..
- We got a winner. - We got a winner.
- I said, we got a winner. - We got a winner!
We got a winner!
She's a flight attendant from Washington, DC.
Please welcome Mary Kellington.
Juice by Mary! Juice by Mary! Whoa...
Harold, please, not again the TV.
Ma! Come on, Ma!
Why do you have to make a big deal outta this?
You know you'll get the set back
in a couple of hours.
Why you gotta make me feel so guilty, Ma?!
Jesus! What are you doing?
Trying to get me to break my own mother's set?
Or radiator?
And maybe blow up the house?
Im your own son!Your own flesh and blood!
Is that what you're trying to do? Your son?
Why you play games with my head,
for Christ's sake?
Harold, I wouldn't do that.
The chain isn't for you. It's for the robbers.
Then why won't you come out?
See what I mean? See how you always upset me, Ma?
Christ's sake.
Ma?
Ma!
Come on out. Please, Ma?
Ah, screw it!
This isn't happening.
And if it should be happening,
it would be all right.
So don't worry, Seymour. It'll all work out.
You'll see already. In the end, it's all nice.
Shit, man.
That motherfucker's starting
to look a little seedy.
You particular all of a sudden?
I don't care my girlfriend go hell,
just as long as we get our bread.
Just give me a hand, Tyrone.
Look at that.
- Hello. - Hi.
Fuck, the table too!
What do you want for me?
You want me to schlep it on my back?
- You got a friend.
- I ain't my leper's schlepper shit.
Such a son.
Your mother needs you
like a moose needs a hat rack.
Shit, man.
This is some boss scag, baby.
- I mean, dynamite.
- Oh, man, it's something else.
You know what we need to do?
We need to get us a piece of this Brody shit,
cut it up and off it!
We could double our money... easy.
They maybe buy some pieces
and we got some whole other never shit coming off
That'd be righteous.
I'll bet in no time off
we'd get a pound of pure
straight from Sal the Geep.
Oooh!
That's what I'm talking about, baby - no hassles.
- How's it goin'? - What's up, buddy?
- The usual? - Yeah, sounds good.
Anything else? Huh?
- Anything else? - Ah, no.
Nothing. I'm all right.
- Good afternoon, Mrs Goldfarb.
- Good afternoon, Mr Rabinowitz.
Although I'm not so sure how good it is. And you?
- What can I say? You want your TV?
- Yes, if you don't mind.
Mrs Goldfarb, can I ask you a question?
You won't take it personal?
How many years we know each other?
Who's to count?
Why not tell ready the police?
Maybe they could talk to Harry.
- He wouldn't be stealing no more the TV.
- I couldn't do that.
Harry's my only child. He's all I have.
Thank you, Mr Rabinowitz.
'Join us in creating excellence. JUICE!'
'You have more passion for living.'
'Be excited! Be, be excited!
'Be excited! Be, be excited!'
'They got the juice?'
- 'Yeah, they got the juice!' - 'Juice it up.'
'Hello? Who is it?'
Aw, shit. Now what?
Hello?
- 'Mrs Sara Goldfarb?' - Me. Speaking.
This is lyle Russell from Maylin and Block.
- I'm not interested.
- 'Wait. I'm not selling anything.
'I just want to offer you a chance
to be on television.'
Television?
'That's right, Mrs Goldfarb. Congratulations!'
- look, I don't have any...
- 'I don't want money Mrs Goldfarb.
'I'm calling to tell you you've already won.
'Maylin and Block discovers contestants
for TV shows.
'You've been chosen from a long list -
'meaning, you've already won.'
- Ohh... - 'Yes, Mrs Goldfarb.'
I never thought I'd be on television. I'm just...
'That's right. You, on television.
'We'll send you the necessary information.
'Goodbye, congratulations and take care.'
But I don't get it.
Why are you so hard on your folks?
I mean, they give you everything.
They hook you up with an apartment,
a croaker shrink.
Which is fine, you know. It's great. It's just...
money is never what I really wanted from them,
you know?
That's pretty much all they have to give.
Why don't you get away from 'em?
- How am I gonna do that? - I don't know.
What about your clothes?
Your sketches are great. Open up a store.
- I can't. - Why not?
When will I have time to hang with you?
- Well! So where's the party?
- When I tell you, you're gonna die.
This is a tough one.
I got a great diet book.
Hey.
They're coming.
'Be excited! Be, be excited!'
I thought I'd catch a little sun today.
Really? Well, in a box you'll catch it.
Just relax and think how gorgeous
you'll look with your new red hair.
Today the hair, tomorrow the sun.
Anybody wanna waste some time?
'Angel says this is time wish do it now.'
- 'she'll call Brody tomorrow.' - 'whos Brody?'
-that's my sweet connects
-'He gets unbelievable shit.'
- 'Righteous.'
- 'look, we got this idea.' - 'What is it?'
'Get a piece of stuff,
cut it up and double our money.no problem'
'Then get a pound of pure and retire.
'You know what that means.'
'We get off hard knocks and on easy street.'
What's the catch?
That's a red. I mean, that's a red.
It's not a red red, but that's a red. It's a red.
- Red? - Yeah. It's a red.
- You're telling me that's red? - Yeah.
Then what's orange?
If this is a red, I want to know - what's orange?
Well, it could be...
that it's a little orange too.
You know something?
I always thought
you were the most beautiful girl I ever seen.
Really?
Ever since I first saw you.
That's nice, Harry.
That makes me feel really good.
Other people have told me that before,
and it was meaningless.
Why?
Because you thought they were pulling your leg?
No, no, not like that. I mean...
I don't know.
I don't know or even care if they were.
Just from them it was...
just meaningless, you know?
When you say it, I hear it.
I really hear it.
Somebody like you
could really make things all right for me.
You think?
What is it?
Remember when I told you about the store?
Yeah.
I've been thinking about it and...
I put together some numbers and...
and it's not impossible!
I mean, you know, you could do it.
You should do it!
I mean, we could do it together.
What do you think?
Stop already.
You'll feel better in the red dress than
in the cheese Danish.
'Three things changed my life. Three.'
'Number one! No red meat!'
'Think about it. What do they stick in red meat?
'I ate red meat to the point
where I would eat it... right off, raw.
'I loved my meat! I turned it around.
'You need to be committed.
You need to be passionate.
'No red meat for 30 days. No red meat!
'Three things is all I did to change my life.
Three things.'
Ada told us. It's gorgeous.
We're gonna make it darker tomorrow.
- Why? - To go with my red dress.
- But it's looking like Madonna.
- It's not Madonna.
And neither is this.
But soon - I'm going on a diet.
- What diet? - Eggs and grapefruit.
- I was on that. Lots of luck. - It's not so bad.
- How long you been on it? - All day.
All day! It's one o'clock!
- Thinking thin. - She's thinking thin.
My louise, she lost 50lbs just like that.
- like what? - Poof!
Did you put her in a sweatbox?
She went to a doctor. He gave her pills.
You don't want to eat.
So? You mean, I'm sitting here
not thinking about pastrami on rye?
Don't talk like that when someone's on a diet.
Big deal. I'll sneak another wedge of grapefruit.
- I'm thinking thin! - Ooh, Sara, the mailman.
Sara Goldfarb? You have something for me?
I'm expecting something.
Goldfarb, Goldfarb. Sara Goldfarb.
- Is that it? - That's it!
- Come on. - I gotta get my stuff.
- All right. - I can tell you.
Your name. Put your name.
S-A-R-A G-O-L-D...
F-A-R-B!
Dynamite?
It's dynamite.
A-ha! Dynamite!
All right, we on our way.
- Brody's man says it's fine shit.
- All right, man.
- Here we go. - Hey, Ty?
- let's do this right, man.
- Come on, baby. Naturally.
- Hurry, hurry. Let's hurry.
- I wonder when you'll hear.
- Hi! - I wanna come with you!
Maybe they'll send you to
the Tavern On The Green with the stars.
Yeah, eggs and grapefruit at Tavern On The Green.
- I hope they have that.
- Hurry before the mailman comes.
- Here we are. - Mail it!
Oh, Sara!
- There it is, Jim. - Huh?
- There it is, baby. - Oh, shit!
- Shall we try it? - Wait, Ty.
Look, this is our chance to make it big.
We play it right, we can get a pound of pure.
But if we get wasted...
- we'll fuck it up. - Right on.
Hey, look, I ain't trying to jive you, Jim.
I dont wanna be running the streets my whole life
my nose runnin' down to my chin.
All I'm sayin' is take a little taste
so we know how much to cut.
It's business.
Yeah, fair enough.
Shit...
'Thank you! Three things is all I did.
'30 days is all it takes.
'Number two! No refined sugar!
'Now, sugar's everywhere.
'You know they even put sugar in bottled water?
'I was sick with sugar! That was my medicine.
'It nurtured my spiralling brain
that felt I was a loser.'
'Juice by you!'
'Rule two is no refined sugar.
'Sodas? Don't even think about sodas any more.
'No sucking candies. None of that.
Just stay away from it.
'No refined sugar. For 30 days.'
'I'm gonna eat right.
'I am gonna pick up my spirits
and I am gonna try!
'I found hope.
And in that hope, I found a way...'
Shut up!
'Hello?'
- Rosie? - 'Yeah.'
- Sara. - 'Yeah?'
I need the number of that doctor.
I don't understand why you gotta see him.
Cut the son of a bitch loose, for Christ's sake.
Because he'll tell my parents
that I've stopped therapy.
They're already thinking of cutting me off.
Harry, I'm not gonna sleep with him.
I'm gonna come home after the concert.
You're jealous!
Harry - jealous?
- Put your arms around me. - No.
You are so stubborn! Put your arms around me.
Stop that!
- I'll suck your eyeballs out. - Mm-hm.
Well...
I'm disappointed that you're indisposed.
Is Anita out of town or something?
Why do you ask?
I was just wondering if she was "indisposed".
No.
She's fine, thank you.
Actually, she's in Florida.
- Can I ask you something, Arnold? - Of course.
Anything. What?
- You just have something here. - Gone?
A little bit, a little bit lower.
It's OK. Don't worry. It's much better.
Arnold!
How are you, Mrs Goldfarb?
How am I? Enormous. That's why I'm here.
- I've seen much worse. - Oh... thank you.
- How's your hearing and vision? - I have both.
The doctor will be with you shortly.
- You're a little overweight. - A little?
I have 50lbs I'm willing to donate.
We can take care of that. No problem.
We're on our way, baby.
We are on our way!
God, It was great out there.
I mean, everybody is thirsty.
Come to me.
Harry! I am so glad.
Naturally.
Purple in the morning.
Blue in the afternoon.
orange in the evening.
There's my three meals, Mr Smarty-pants.
And green at night. Just like that.
one, two, three, four.
Come back to bed, baby.
Come on now, Alice. Got plenty of time for that.
Right now
I'm grooving with these new mirrors I got.
Oooh!
I told ya, Mom, one day I'd make it.
You don't have to make anything, my sweet.
You just have to love your mama, huh?
What ya doin', baby?
Huh?
- What ya doin', baby? - Nothin'.
Just thinkin' about you.
About the nasty things I'm about to do to ya.
Bitch, get over here!
Ty, you scare me to death.
No, I wouldn't scare you.
I don't wanna scare nobody.
All I want out of life
is a bit of peace and happiness. That's all.
Right now...
you're the finest fox I ever laid my eyes on.
- That's what I'll do. - Hmm?
For my mother.
I've been thinking about
getting something for her.
Like... a present or something.
But I didn't know what I was gonna get,
until now.
- And? - I finally asked myself, right,
what's her fix?
Television, right?
If ever there's a TV junkie, it's the old lady.
I owe her a new set,
with all the wear and tear it got
being schlepped back and forth to old Abe's.
You really love her, don't you?
I-I guess so. You know?
Most of the time I just want her to be happy.
Let's go get it now.
Let's push off first.
It's early, Harry.
We shouldn't get going till tonight.
'Be excited. Be, be excited.
'Be excited.
'Be committed and be passionate.'
'I am a living testament. 65 lbs thinner.
I feel great!
'Number three. Ohhh, number three!
'This drives most people crazy.
'This is easy so far.'
- That is thin! - She's not the same person.
I can almost zip the red dress.
I've almost got the zipper up.
- The mailman! - Oh!
When I see it I'll wave it all over the place.
- Are you sure? - Yeah, I'm sure.
- What did he say?
- Don't worry, Sara, it'll come.
Yeah, don't worry. It'll come.
It's Harry!
Harry, oh!
Hey, Ma, easy. You'll crush me, for Christ sakes.
- Come inside. - Hello.
- Hi, Harry! Hello! - We'll have a little visit.
So, how are you, Harry? You look so good.
- You want something to eat? - No, Ma.
A little nosh, a piece of cake?
I could go and get something if you want.
I don't have anything in the house,
but Ada would have.
A cupcake? You want something to eat?
No, no, Ma, nothing. Please, sit.
You're making me dizzy, for Christ's sake.
You notice anything, huh? You notice I'm slimmer?
Yeah, I guess you are.
25lbs, I lost. 25lbs! Can you believe it?
- And that's only the beginning.
- That's great, Ma That's readly great.
I'm really happy for you.
But will you sit? Please.
I'm sorry I haven't been around in a while,
Ma, but I've been busy.
Yeah? You got a good job? You're doing well?
- Yeah, good, real good. - What kind of business?
Well, I'm sort of a distributor like,
for a big importer.
- Ohh! I'm so happy for you!
- Ma... Easy. You're killin' me.
Jesus, what, you been lifting weights?
- I knew you could do that. - You were right.
Now maybe you'll meet a nice girl
and have a baby?
Well, I already met one.
Ma, don't go ape shit.
- Who is she? Who's her parents? - You know her.
- Marion? Marion Silver. Remember? - Oh, Silver!
of course. Manhattan Beach.
House on the esplanade. Garment business.
He's big in women's undies.
Before you go bouncing all over again
and make me forget, just...
What I wanna tell you is that
I got you a present.
I don't need a present. Just have a baby.
Will you let me tell you what I got ya?
Will ya, Ma?
Christ, you are really something else today,
you know that?
Look, I know...
Well...
I'm sorry for being such a bastard.
I wanna make it up.
I mean,
I know I can't change anything that's happened,
but I want you to know that...
That I love ya, and that I'm sorry.
And I want you to be happy.
So I got you a brand-new TV set.
It's gonna be delivered in a couple of days.
It's from Macy's!
oh, Harry!
Your father'd be so happy
if he could see what you're doing
for your mother.
See that, Seymour?
You see how good your son is?
He knows
what it's like for his mother living all alone.
No one to visit her.
Hey, Ma.
- You on uppers? - What?
You're on uppers.
You're on diet pills, ain't you?
I told you. I'm going to a specialist.
That's what I thought! You're on speed, ain't ya?
Harry, I'm goin' to a doctor.
- Does he give you pills?
- Of course. He's a doctor.
- What kind of pills?
- A purple, a blue, an orange...
I mean, like what's in 'em?
Oh, Harry, I'm Sara Goldfarb,
not Albert Einstein.
How should I know?
Does it make you feel good and give you pep?
Well... yeah, a little.
Ma, I can hear ya grinding your teeth.
- That goes away at night. - At night?
Yeah, when I take the green one.
30 minutes I'm asleep. Poof.
Ma, Ma, ya gotta cut that stuff loose.
I'm tellin' ya, it's no good.
What do you mean it's no good? 25lbs I've lost.
So what? You wanna be a dope fiend?
Dope fiend? Am I foaming at the mouth?
He's a nice doctor.
I am telling you, he's no good.
How come you know so much?
How come you know more than a doctor?
Believe me, Ma, I know. All right?
You'll get strung out for creat sick.
Ah, come on! I almost fit in my red dress.
The one I wore to your high school graduation.
The one your father liked so much.
oh,
I remember how he looked at me in that red dress.
Ma, what's the big deal about the red dress?
I'm going to wear it at...
You don't know!
I'm gonna be on television.
I got a call and an application...
Come on, Ma, who's pulling your leg?
No, no, no. I'm tellin' ya.
I'm gonna be a contestant on television.
They haven't told me when yet,
but you'll be proud
when you see your mother in her red dress on TV.
What is the big deal?
Those pills will kill you before you get on.
"Big deal? "
You drove up in a cab.
Did you see who had the best seat?
I'm somebody now, Harry.
Everybody likes me.
Soon...
millions of people will see me
and they'll all like me.
I'll tell them about you...
and your father.
How good he was to us.
Remember?
It's a reason to get up in the morning.
It's a reason to lose weight,
to fit in the red dress.
It's a reason to smile.
It makes tomorrow all right.
What have I got, Harry?
Hmm?
Why should I even make the bed
or wash the dishes?
I do them, but why should I?
I'm alone.
Your father's gone, you're gone.
I got no one to...
care for.
What have I got, Harry?
I'm lonely.
I'm old.
You got friends, Ma.
It's not the same.
They don't need me.
I like the way I feel.
I like thinking about the red dress...
and the television and you and your father.
Now when I get the sun, I smile.
I'll come and visit, Ma.
Now that I'm straight,
m-my business is going good, I'll come.
Me and Marion, we'll come for dinner.
Good. You bring her.
I'll make you mushroom soup and a roast.
That sounds great, Ma. That sounds great.
- I'll call ahead, all right? - OK.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you have a nice girl
and your own business. I'm glad.
I gotta go, Ma.
I got an appointment in Manhattan in a little bit
but I'll be back.
- OK, y-you still got your key?
- Yeah, I got it, Ma.
Bye, Son.
Brody says you comin' up quick.
oh. Thanks, man.
He says you're smart,
you're loyal and you're not a junkie.
Brody wants to promote you.
Give you more responsibility. Interested?
Yeah, yeah!
Shit, yeah, man.
Brody says, you fuck him, I kill you.
- I got that. - Remember that.
Shit! You got a white driver!
Fuck!
What the fuck?
Don't move!
I love you, Harry.
You make me feel like a person.
Like I'm me...
and I'm beautiful.
You are beautiful.
You're the most beautiful girl in the world.
You're my dream.
'No, I'm certain. I've checked again.'
But maybe you gave me a weaker one last time.
'That isn't possible.
They're all the same potency.'
But something isn't the same.
'You're becoming adjusted to them.
It's nothing to worry about, OK?'
- 'We got a winner!' - 'We got a winner!'
'She's beautiful, with a winning sense of humour
'and magical smile.
'From Brighton Beach, Brooklyn, let's welcome
'Mrs Sara Goldfarb!'
'Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Ohh, Sara!
'Sara's got juice! Sara's got juice! Ohh, Sara!'
Love, Tyrone C.
Get your shit together. You made bail.
How much?
Most of our cash. You're up for consortin'.
oh, shit, man!
Angel says
there's a war between the Italians and Blacks.
Sal the Geep is keeping the shit in Florida
until Brody's gone.
Shit.
- No one's got a thing. - Except Big Tim.
Shit. Let's go see him.
He only givin' up for pussy.
What?
Pussy. He's hooked on it, man.
I'd give him all he wants.
He said I ain't cute enough.
'Come on, number three!
'This drives most people crazy.
'They're not gonna like it.
'This is easy so far!
Give it up for 30 days, it will...'
You all right?
Yeah. It was just a bad dream.
Want some water?
Maybe we should dip in now.
Come on! I already told you, all right?
It's all we have.
Tyrone is gonna score in the morning, Harry.
I don't know, it's...
it's a bitch out there.
It'll be OK.
It'll be OK, Harry.
Yeah...
I guess so.
I love you, Harry.
What's the problem? The weight's fine.
The weight's fine, I'm not.
The refrigerator...
Something wrong?
Everything's...
all mixed up.
- Confused... - Nothing to worry about.
Get this filled. Make an appointment for a week.
Well?
Ty ain't found nothin' yet.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Well, you have to do something, Harry.
It's your fault we don't have anything.
- What? - You were all hot last night.
- That is such bullshit!
- We could've had something...
Was I supposed to watch you push off
and not go myself?
Don't put it all on me, OK?
Don't worry, man. We'll fill it up again.
Things'll get better,
then we'll be fillin' the box back up, you know?
So, you wanna hear the news?
What news?
You got your good news, you got your bad news.
Shoot.
Good news is,
there's gonna be some prime on the street.
- Really? - Mm-hm.
Who told you that?
- Angel. - Yeah?
Sal the Geep sent word
to let a couple of keys go for Christmas,
him being a good Christian and all,
not wantin' bad feelin' during the season.
- You believe it? - Well, I did...
till I heard the bad news.
Yeah?
Price is double. You have to cop for weight.
- At least a half a piece. - How much?
- Two. - Two?
- That's fuckin' insane! - What you gonna do?
Man ain't gonna lay no nickel bag on ya.
Where we gonna get two?
You mean Arnold?
Well, your parents won't even return your call.
I haven't seen him in months.
- So? He's still callin', ain't he?
- I don't know.
Look, I don't know what else to do.
It's our last chance to get back on track!
We won't have to squabble
and make the freezing scene every day!
We need the bread.
Getting the money is not the problem, Harry.
What is the problem?
I don't know what I'll have to do to get it.
Look...
Baby...
we'll be back in business in no time.
We'll start movin' again,
and we'll start savin'.
It'll be perfect, just like it was.
I promise, Marion.
You'll see.
No, I've just, uh..
. I've had this flu forever, it seems like.
- Are you depressed?
- No, it's nothing like that.
I've been, uh... I've been really busy.
Actually, I've been designing... non-stop.
Wonderful. Glad to hear you've been productive.
To be perfectly frank,
I was a little surprised to hear from you.
- Is there something wrong? - No. Why?
Well, it's usually the case...
from someone you haven't heard from.
Everything's fine.
Actually,
I have a favour to ask.
You smug fuck!
What is it?
I need some money.
May I ask what for?
- Could you turn the light off?
- Why do you want the light off?
I just do.
- You never did before. - Please, Arnold.
- Where is everybody? - I don't know, man.
All Angel said was meet at Waldbaum's.
- Is this the right Waldbaum's?
- Yeah, I'm positive.
You just watch my back, and I'll watch yours.
- What are we supposed to do now? - Hey.
Everyone and their mother.
The truck's gonna be here. Back up.
Back up.
Come back!
Stupid fuckin' junkie!
We're fucked! We are fucked.
Sitting in that hot-ass sun
while we sit here ass deep in motherfuckin' snow.
What if we went down there?
- Are you serious? - Why not?
What the fuck are you sayin'?
We ask some room clerk at some hotel for a connection?
You saying you can't nose out some dope
when it's around?
Man, we got nothin' to lose. It's wide open.
And if we get there right away
we can name our own price,
and have those fools cover the street for us.
Yeah, man.
Last summer was a motherfuckin' ball, huh, Jim?
Just seems like a thousand years ago
since last summer, man.
It'll be like that again, man.
I could get Angel to get us a short...
if we promise him some dynamite scag.
Thank God. Where have you been?
Where the hell you think I've been?
- Where's the score? - We had a bit of a problem.
I mean, everything was goin' good, and then...
- some dumb-ass junkie... - Did what?
Some dumb-ass junkie did what?! You fucked up?!
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- You promised it was gonna be OK.
I fucked that sleaze-bag.
I put myself through hell for you!
- There's nothing out there!
- I don't give a shit! Fucking loser!
You wanna be sure we have some extra?
Ty told me about a guy holding some weight.
But he ain't sellin' it!
'Yeah?'
- Gimme that guy's number. - 'What guy?'
- The guy who likes broads! - 'Why?'
Just gimme the number!
'All right. 934-8777.'
You worried so much, go fix yourself up with him!
You won't have to fuckin' wait
and I won't freeze my ass off the fucking street!
Fuck you.
'All right, we got a winner.'
- 'We got a winner.' - 'We got a winner.'
'She's beautiful,
with a winning sense of humour and smile.
'She'll win your heart!
'From Brighton Beach, Brooklyn,
'please give a juicy welcome to
our own Mrs Sara Goldfarb!'
'Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Ohh, Sara!'
'Ohh, Sara!'
'It's a pleasure to be here.'
'It's a pleasure to have you.
And that is one smashing dress.'
'Thank you. Tappy.
I would like to say hello
to my husband, Seymour,
'and my beautiful, successful son Harold...'
'I hope you're in love.
'Please come and see me,
and bring Marion, won't you?'
'I'm sure he'll be here soon.
'It's almost that time. Are you ready?'
'I'm ready, Tappy.'
'Not to worry. Not to worry.'
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
- What do you want? - Oh, Tappy!
'Join us in creating excellence.
'Oh, I thought you'd never ask.'
Look at this.
- It's disgusting. - What do you expect?
Could you do any better?
Look at this.
It's an old building.
It hasn't been painted in years.
I'm old! Alone!
You don't understand.
Please. I'll explain.
What is that? No, I don't want that!
What are you doing? Get away from me!
- Ready, Mrs Goldfarb. - Ready for What?
Three, two...
What am I supposed to do?
Feed me!
Feed him yourself.
Feed me, Sara.
Feed me, Sara!
Feed me, Sara! Feed me, Sara!
I just wanna be on television! Please!
Thank you, Angel.
Whoo-hoo!
Sure hope this motherfucker works.
My ass could use some heat.
- How long this trip's gonna take?
- We'll make it in a day.
A day? Shit!
California, here we come.
It's Florida, Ty. Florida.
California, Florida...
Either way, your pale ass getting a tan.
Ah!
Does this train go to Madison Avenue?!
Do you know Maylin and Block?
I have their address. It's on Madison Avenue.
- I'm gonna be on television. - You're whacked!
Hey! Hey! Hello?
Do you know if this train goes to Madison Avenue?
I'm gonna be on television!
I just have to find out when.
Florida?
When is he gonna be back?
A few days? Angel, what am I supposed to do?
Please, you gotta help me.
Oh, come on, I can get you money.
Angel, there's gotta be something. Anything.
Help me.
Why aren't you calling me?
I have to know when I'm gonna be on television.
I'm Sara Goldfarb.
And you should tell me
when I'm gonna be on television.
Just sit for a moment. I'll ring them.
I just wanna know when.
Maybe you lost my card!
Please, have a look, and you'll tell me.
It's not the prizes. I'll give them away.
I just wanna be on the show.
I've waited so long...
to be on with my Harry and my grandson.
Here, Mrs Goldfarb, sip this.
Sometimes it takes a while
to get called for a show,
Mrs Goldfarb.
Oh. Oooh.
- Is this her? - Yes.
- Can you walk? - I'm walkin' across the stage!
And you should see my Harry on television.
We're giving the prizes away.
I just wanted to be on the show!
- What's her name? - We think it's Sara Goldfarb.
Tell Seymour to meet me at the beauty parlour.
I've got the red dress that
I wore to Harry's graduation and gold shoes.
oK, Mrs Goldfarb. Here we go.
- One, two, three...
Let's take it nice and easy.
'Yeah?'
Hi...
Tell Rose I'm going to be on television.
Whoo.
oh, shit!
God damn! How long you had that?
- Just a few days.
- That shit don't look too good.
It don't feel too good either, man.
But a little stuff will take care of that.
Hey! Don't shoot in there!
I'll blow it if I don't.
Fuck it.
oh...
Shit.
- Hi, how are you? Can you hear me?
- Yes, Seymour.
- Take anything?
- I took my red dress and...
- No emergency. Take her to psych.
- Television.
Come on in.
Thanks.
What's your name?
Marion.
Well, what do you know?
Maid Marion.
I'm little John.
Beautiful view.
You know what I like about paddy chicks?
They give good head.
Black broads know nothin' about head.
I don't know why.
Maybe it's to do with some ancient tribal custom.
Come here.
Mmm. Better save some of that energy.
oh, I know it's pretty, baby,
but I didn't take it out for air.
Yeah.
I told your ass, stay away from that arm. See?
I gotta call Marion, man.
That's about to be a long-distance call now.
That's 600 miles!
We are 600 miles closer to Miami.
It's also 600 miles further away from New York.
I know where to get a real nice taste,
though it's more like play. Sunday night?
We're throwing a little gathering.
All good people.
I can't, I'm busy.
Anyway, I'm not really hooked.
Oh, I know, but it's a real nice taste.
I'll see you Sunday, Maid Marion.
OK, just try and answer my questions.
- When did you start taking pills?
- Oh, the summer.
- You started last summer?
- I got the best place in the sun.
- Ada fixed my hair.
- Everything is gonna be all right.
We'll get you fixed up in no time.
- Hold tight, man. - I can't fucking cut it.
I gotta do something about my arm.
Let me see what it looks like.
oh, damn, Jim!
oh, man.
That's one ugly motherfucker.
- I gotta call Marion. - Fuck that.
We gotta get you to a hospital, man.
What is that?
I don't want that. I don't want that!
Ah! Oh...
What's the problem?
- It's my arm. My arm is killin' me.
- let's have a look at it.
All right.
I'll be back in a minute.
I wanna play blackjack all night long.
So I make up this routine.
I say, "you go ahead. I don't feel good."
Sure enough, they leave...
Ready? One, two and three.
As soon as they leave,
I go running back to the casino,
sit at my blackjack table.
I am there for the whole night.
Finally, I get up so big,
I got five $100 black chips in my pocket.
I swear to God. The hours are going by.
I'm laying back, hittin' on hard 17 s.
It was beautiful.
Next thing I know,
this security guard
is sitting there telling me I have to leave.
I'm like, "Why you telling me I have to leave?"
He says, "You have to leave because..."
Swallow.
You have to eat.
If we're gonna get you healthy you have to eat.
Work with the attendants.
I'm gonna try some new medications.
- Hello. - 'Marion.'
Harry?
'Marion, I've been thinking about you so much.
'Are you OK?'
- When you comin' home? - Soon.
When?
Soon.
- 'You holdin' out all right?' - Harry?
Can you come today?
Yeah.
I'll come.
'I'll come today.'
You just wait for me, all right?
- OK, Harry. - 'I'm coming back, Marion.'
- Yeah. - 'Marion?'
Yeah?
I'm really sorry, Marion.
I know.
Mrs Goldfarb?
You all right?
Um, so, Mrs Goldfarb,
we've tried several medications,
and you don't seem to be responding.
I believe we might want to
try some alternative methods.
We've had excellent results with ECT in the past.
Um... So if I can just...
get your John Hancock...
we'll get underway.
Great. Thanks.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
I need a doctor, man.
My friend is sick. Give him some help, please.
I can't take it, man! My arm! My fuckin' arm!
Help me!
Help us! Somebody fuckin' help us, please!
Maid Marion. Welcome.
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
Fellas, meet Marion.
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
Show time.
OK for work. Can you hear me? Can you see me?
Yes. Oof!
Say, "sir". Goddam New York dope fiend niggers.
Learn some manners.
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
- Got a mouthpiece.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
Says something's wrong with his arm.
He won't be puttin' any more dope in that.
- Smells worse than he do. - Test.
Get him over to hospital.
Ready? And... one.
That's the trouble with you dope fiends.
You got a rotten attitude. You know that man?
- So what are we gonna do now? - Ass to ass.
Ass to ass!
Put your spineless back into it! Come on!
Ready? And... two!
Ass to ass!
- Put it in there! - That's it.
Nice and easy.
Mashed potatoes!
Here's the close. I need one gram. Bingo.
Don't give up. Don't give up.
Move it, move it, move it!
OK.
Ready? And... three!
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!
We're gonna take it off at the shoulder.
Saw.
Marion!
It's all right.
Don't worry. You're in a hospital.
- Marion? - Who's that?
She'll be sent for. She'll come.
- No. - No?
No, she won't.
She'll come.
- We got a winner. - We got a winner.
- Got a winner! - We got a winner.
Our next winner is that delightful personality,
from Brighton Beach, Brooklyn.
Please, give a juicy welcome
to Mrs Sara Goldfarb!
I'm delighted to tell you
that you have won the grand prize!
- Oh, no! - let me tell you what you've won.
He has a sweet smile and his own business.
He just got engaged,
and is about to get married this summer.
Please give a warm and juicy welcome.
Harry Goldfarb!
Juice by Harry! Juice by Harry!
ohh, Harry's got juice! Harry's got juice!
ohh, Harry!
- I love you, Harry. - I love you too, Ma.